Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretion 2008 - Series IV: Professional Projects, 158958
  - Subseries I: Writing Files, 1988-2003; 159054
    - "Freakathon" Scrapbook Materials 2 of 2, Undated; 159076 (Box 20, Folder 137)
    - "Freakathon" Research, Magic and Circuses, Undated; 159075 (Box 20, Folder 138)
    - "Freakathon" Research, Vacation/Resorts, Undated; 159074 (Box 20, Folder 139)
    - "Freakathon" Notes and Script, 2003; 159073 (Box 20, Folder 140)
    - "Music," Lyrics and Notation, Undated; 159072 (Box 20, Folder 141)
    - "Sarah's Songs", Undated; 159071 (Box 20, Folder 142)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1994; 159070 (Box 20, Folder 143)
    - Notebook, 1994; 159069 (Box 20, Folder 144)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1994-1996; 159068 (Box 20, Folder 145)
    - Notebook, "Sundance", 1996-1997; 159067 (Box 20, Folder 146)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1996; 159066 (Box 21, Folder 147)
    - Notebook, 1996; 159065 (Box 21, Folder 148)
    - Day to Day To-Do Lists, Prep for Interviews, 1996-1997; 159064 (Box 21, Folder 149)
    - Notebook, 1996-1997; 159063 (Box 21, Folder 150)
    - Notebook, To-Do Lists, 1997; 159062 (Box 21, Folder 151)
    - Notebook, 1997; 159061 (Box 21, Folder 152)
    - Notebook, 1998-1999; 159060 (Box 21, Folder 153)
    - Notebook, circa 2000; 159059 (Box 21, Folder 154)
    - Notebook, 2000-2001; 159058 (Box 21, Folder 155)
    - "Sarah - Living on 16th St. NY" Notebook, 2001; 159057 (Box 21, Folder 156)
    - Notebook, circa 2002; 159056 (Box 21, Folder 157)
    - Notebook, circa 2002; 159055 (Box 21, Folder 158)
  - Subseries J: Media Originals, 158959
    Subseries J contains donated media elements related to the previous subseries. Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - "Sarah's Films" - [1] Making of the Diner / Diner Video [2] What I Learned In A Buick Station Wagon / Road Movie [3] Disco Film [4] Java Jive [5] Eiffel Tower High, Undated; 159053 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0315)
    - "Sarah's Films for the Family" - [1] The Making of the Diner Scene from Road Movie [2] Road Movie (or What I Learned in a Buick Station Wagon) [3] The Adventures of Sweet Miss The Disco Years [4] Film for Mom [5] Eiffel Tower High, Undated; 159052 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0316)
    - "Road Movie, What I Learned in a Buick Station Wagon", Undated; 159051 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0372)
    - "Wild Sound for What I Learned", Undated; 159050 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0492)
    - "The Adventures of Sweet Miss The Disco Years", Undated; 159049 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0397)
    - "Eiffel Tower High", Undated; 159048 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0339)
    - "Rough Cut Films on Video" - [1] Sweet Miss [2] Paula Gotlesman's NY, Undated; 159047 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0349)
    - "Sleaze Auditions 3/00", 2000; 159046 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0317)
    - "Sleaze, Tape # 1", Undated; 159045 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0382)
    - "Sleaze, Tape #2", Undated; 159044 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0383)
    - "Sleaze, Tape #3", Undated; 159043 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0384)
      Format: DV Cam, Donated Element
    - "Sleaze Soundtrack - Tape #1", Undated; 159042 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0480)
    - "Sleaze Soundtrack - Tape #2", Undated; 159041 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0481)
    - "Sleaze, 5th Night Reading 4/11/00", 2000; 159040 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0482)
    - "Sarah Jacobson Music Video Reel" [1] Man or Astroman - Sferic Waves [2] The Jack Saints - Brain Bats from Venus [3] Fluffy - Vomit [4] Mary Jane Trailer, Undated; 159039 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0368)
      Format: Video Cassette, Donated Element
    - "Man or Astroman Spferic Waves Music Video", Undated; 159038 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0392)
    - "The Jack Saints Video - Brain Brats From Venus, Master", Undated; 159037 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0341)
    - "Fluffy: Music Video", Undated; 159036 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0459)
    - "Reunion #2 8/99", 1999; 159035 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0431)
    - "Reunion #3 8/99", 1999; 159034 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0432)
    - "High School Reunion", Undated; 159033 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0435, Case 157.0435)
    - "Sarah Jacobson Director's Reel" - [1] "Sferic Waves" - Man or Astroman? [2] "Teenage Serial Killer" - film excerpt [3] "Vomit" - Fluffy [4] "Mary Jane's Not a Virgin" - film excerpt, Undated; 159032 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0364)
      TRT: 00:10:00
    - "Sarah Jacobson Producer/Writer 2/2003", 159031 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0365)
    - "Sarah's Reel" / Sarah Jacobson Producer/Writer Reel 2-19-03 - [1] Cecil B. Demented [2] Playing for Peanuts [3] Phantom Planet [4] Adam [5] Summer Concert [6] Stains, 2003; 159030 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0402)
    - "TV Moments Segments" / "My 100 Greatest TV Moments", Undated; 159029 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0328)
    - "Sarah's 100 TV Moments Segments" - [1] #99 Cop Rock, #96 Public Image Limited on Bandstand, #93 Courtney [2] #35 Charlie Brown Christmas, #30 Bowie and Bing [3] #21 Homerpallooza [4] #46 Lennon/Cosell, Undated; 159028 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0366)
    - "100 TV Moments Segments for VH1", Undated; 159027 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0391)
    - "Paul Cook Interview 5-8-98", 1998; 159026 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0369)
    - "Paul Cook", Undated; 159025 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0370)
    - "My First Time," Women Directors' First Films, Tamra Davis, Esther Bell, Undated; 159024 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0347)
    - "Oh the Ladies" Ep. 2 - Film Front Interview, Undated; 159023 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0325)
    - "Women Director's Summit, 50/50's Meeting", Undated; 159022 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0388)
    - 50/50 Part II / "Our First Time," "Cowboy Jesus Fork" by Suki Hawley, Undated; 159021 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0389)
    - 50/50 Show "My First Time" [1] "Discharge" - Jamie Babbitt [2] "Sleep" - Helen Stickler [3] "Mary in the Water" - Tamra Davis [4] "The Slap" - Tamara Hernandez [5] "Sweet Miss The Disco Years" - Sarah Jacobson [6] "The Air Globes" - Patricia Cardoso [7] "How to Make an Oliver Stone Movie" - Mary Harron, Undated; 159020 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0390)
    - "Trackers - Summer Concert Safety", Undated; 159019 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0327)
    - "DV 3 I Trackers - Hellstock 8/99, Suki Hawley, Tonya Lewis #1, producer Sarah Jacobson", 1999; 159018 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0420)
    - "DV 4 II Trackers - Hellstock 8/99, Tanya Lewis #2, producer Sarah Jacobson", 1999; 159017 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0421)
    - "DV 5 Intern I, Concert 6/9/00", 2000; 159016 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0395)
    - "DV 6 Intern II, Simone & Sharon Concert Safety", Undated; 159015 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0396)
    - "Hellstock #1, Sarah & Cindy 8/99", 1999; 159014 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0422)
    - "Hellstock #2, Sarah & Cindy 8/99", 1999; 159013 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0423)
    - "Hellstock, Cynthia, Cindy 8/99", 1999; 159012 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0424)
    - "Hellstock, Jessica, Cynthia 8/99", 1999; 159011 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0425)
    - "Summer Concert Safety Master", Undated; 159010 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0394)
      Format: DVCam, Donated Element
    - "Woodstock", Undated; 159009 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0407)
    - "Woodstock 2", Undated; 159008 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0408)
    - "DV 14 Woodstock TV", Undated; 159007 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0409)
    - "RI: Phantom Planet Segments", Undated; 159006 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0367)
    - "RI: Phantom Planet", Undated; 159005 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0393)
    - "Phunky Bitches #1 5/21/00", 2000; 159004 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0386)
    - "Phunky Bitches #2 5/21/00", 2000; 159003 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0387)
    - "DV 16 Phunky Bitch B-Roll 6/20/00", 159002 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0385)
    - "Sarah's Pseudo Reel" - [1] Cecil B. Demented [2] Blackout Books [3] Toys in Babeland [4] Radical Cheerleaders, Undated; 159001 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0398)
    - "Third Wave B-roll", Undated; 159000 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0440)
    - "3rd Wave - Brdl, Esther Dancing, Carnival w/Scott, Boss Hog, Movie Screening Girl Int, Dictionary", Undated; 158999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0439)
    - "Oxygen Etc. B-Roll Tape A" - [1] Oxygen Office [2] Lots of Black [3] Bluestockings [4] Mixfest [5] Editing [6] Yo Yo Girl [7] Mixfest (Bluestockings Vag. Creme Davis Mr. Lady) 11/99, 1999; 158998 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0441)
    - "S26 - Studio Shot by Kirsten", Undated; 158997 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0426)
    - "S27" - [1] Belly Dancers [2] Club Going [3] No More Prisons Talk, Undated; 158996 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0416)
    - "S28" - No More Prisons Talk, Pt. 2, Undated; 158995 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0417)
    - "Columbia Tape 1 TTV", Undated; 158994 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0418)
    - "Columbia Tape 2 TTV", Undated; 158993 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0419)
    - "CUFF #1 Animal Charm Lakeview 8/99", 1999; 158992 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0410)
    - "CUFF #2 Interview Park 8/99", 1999; 158991 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0411)
    - "CUFF #3 Bowling 8/16/99", 1999; 158990 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0412)
    - "CUFF #4 Bowling, Airport 8/99", 1999; 158989 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0413)
    - "Sarah's Reel Master 2002" [EMPTY], 158988 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0399)
      This is an empty Mini DV Box, it contains the following notation: "w/ Red Aunts Music, Cecil B. Demented, Phantom Planet, Adam the Tastemaker, Summer Concert Safety, Stains"
    - "Sarah's Reel 2002" - [1] Cecil B. Demented [2] Phantom Planet [3] Adam the Tastemaker [3] Summer Concert Safety [4] Making of the Stains, 158987 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0400)
      TRT: 00:08:00
    - "Sarah's Reel 2002 Master 2/21/02" - "w/ Red Aunts Music, Cecil B. Demented, Phantom Planet, Adam, Summer Concert, Stains, 158986 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0401)
    - "Cecil B. Demented 8/9/00", 2000; 158985 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0403)
    - "Sarah's 02 Reel" - [1] Yo yo [2] NYUFF [3] ABC No Rio [4] Audra / ISW [5] Blue Stockings [6] Building Studio [7] 3rd Wave [8] Knitting, 2002; ID: 157.0414; 158984 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0414)
    - "Sarah's '02 Stuff #2" - [1] Tibet [2] Take Back the Decks [3] Circus [4] Pepper Steppers [5] Graffitti [6] Guerilla Girls, 2002; ID: 157.0415; 158983 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0415)
    - "TM: Adam", Undated; ID: 157.0404; 158982 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0404)
      TRT: 00:40:00
    - "TM: Adam, Shana, Tape 2", Undated; ID: 157.0405; 158981 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0405)
      TRT: 00:30:00
    - "Reel Master" - [1] John Waters [2] Crowd Surfing [3] The Stains [4] Take Back the Decks, Undated; ID: 157.0406; 158980 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0406)
    - "#1 Radical Cheerleaders", Undated; ID: 157.0427; 158979 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0427)
    - "#2 Radical Cheerleaders", 2000; ID: 157.0428; 158978 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0428)
    - "BBW / Apartment Before Ladyfest Chicago - Mos Interview, Lady Superstars", Undated; ID: 157.0437; 158977 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0437)
    - "DV 8 Ladyfest Chicago - Weird Band, Radical Cheerlead, Evil Beaver, My Press Speech", Undated; ID: 157.0438; 158976 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0438)
      The case label contains the following notation: "DV 8, Interviews + B Roll, 311 + No Doubt" while the tape inside reads "Ladyfest Chicago."
    - "Letterman Marquee 11/20/02", ID: 157.0442; 158975 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0442)
    - "DV 15 Self Defense / Logos", ID: 157.0443; 158974 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0443)
    - "Ann Powers #1 9/20/99 NY", 1999; ID: 157.0444; 158973 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0444)
    - "Trackers 9/99, Ann Powers #2, Galen NOW #1, producer Sarah Jacobson", 1999; ID: 157.0445; 158972 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0445)
    - "Galen NOW 9/99", 1999; ID: 157.0446; 158971 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0446)
    - "Anton in Mpls 2/01", 2001; ID: 157.0447; 158970 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0447)
    - "David Friedman, Steve Buschemi! LA Trip 4/00", 2000; ID: 157.0448; 158969 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0448)
    - "Gillian Armstrong, AIDS Test 10/99 SF", 1999; ID: 157.0449; 158968 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0449)
    - "Gilman Show, Sell More Books Jack Stevenson, CW, Freeway 2 SF 10/99", 1999; ID: 157.0450; 158967 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0450)
    - "Jim Jarmusch, My Rock Debut CBGBs - Basement DIY Fest 2/21/01", 2001; ID: 157.0451; 158966 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0451)
    - "Sarah St. Vincent 12/31/2003", ID: 157.0452; 158965 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0452)
    - "Thurston Gary, Got a Job Dave Markey 9/23/99 NY", 1999; ID: 157.0453; 158964 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0453)
    - "Willie Brown Nellie 10/6/99 SF", 1999; ID: 157.0454; 158963 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0454)
    - "Baltimore FF '00, Will at Waiting Brooklyn Show", 2000; ID: 157.0457; 158962 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0457)
    - "IKON Modeling Footage", Undated; ID: 157.0460; 158961 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0460)
    - "NY - CMJ Bratmobile, Don Letts Gary 9/99", 1999; ID: 157.0463; 158960 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0463)
- Accretion 2008 - Series V: Miscellaneous Media Originals, 158866
  Conditions Governing Use
  This series includes donated media elements. Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings, 158946
    - "Paula Rambles - This Side", Undated; ID: 157.0483; 158957 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0483)
    - "Please Forward to Sarah, Jan '99, WSIA FM, Michael Horan III", 1999; ID: 157.0484; 158956 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0484)
    - "Annie - Sarah com. pk.", Undated; ID: 157.0485; 158955 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0485)
    - "Sarah on the Alex Bennett Show", Undated; ID: 157.0486; 158954 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0486)
    - "Sarah - Beth Friend - Full Program, [Side A] KNOW Interview, [Side B] A Rainbow Path - Kay Gardner, Music by Melissa Verdio", 1990; ID: 157.0487; 158953 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0487)
    - "KROQ Station Wagon Productions", Undated; ID: 157.0491; 158952 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0491)
    - "Half Moon Bay" KT66/4, Undated; ID: 157.0493; 158951 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0493)
      TRT: 00:03:30
    - "Bat Mitzvah Sarah, Compliments of Temple Israel Men's Club", Undated; ID: 157.0494; 158950 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0494)
    - "Master Phil, Jam", Undated; ID: 157.0495; 158949 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0495)
    - "Sarah Jacobson / Rev 105, Mpls, MN", Undated; ID: 157.0498; 158948 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0498)
    - "Film Close-Ups, Apr. 1", No Year; ID: 157.0499; 158947 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0499)
  - Subseries C: Video Recordings, Independent Media, 158937
    - Godass by Esther Bell, 2000; ID: 157.0340; 158945 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0340)
    - The Films of Jeff Krulik and Friends, Undated; ID: 157.0342; 158944 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0342)
    - The Litter Box by George Kuchar, 1997; ID: 157.0343; 158943 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0343)
    - Metropolitan Monologues by George Kuchar, 2000; ID: 157.0344; 158942 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0344)
    - Munchkins of Melody Manor by George Kuchar, Undated; ID: 157.0345; 158941 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0345)
    - Metallica Drummer, Undated; ID: 157.0346; 158940 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0346)
    - "She Thing" The Judy Spots, Director: S. Benning, Producer: E. Subrin, Undated; ID: 157.0350; 158939 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0350)
    - "3 Student Films" - [1] Shaded [2] Thurs. Kool-Aid [3] Ben, Ali, Allison, Undated; ID: 157.0352; 158938 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0352)
  - Subseries D: Video Recording (VHS), Other - Originals, 158888
    - "PXL - Art School Chicks Save Rock + Roll", Undated; ID: 157.0318; 158936 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0318)
    - "Roller Skating PXL", Undated; ID: 157.0319; 158935 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0319)
    - "Rough Pixel", Undated; ID: 157.0320; 158934 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0320)
    - "Transferred PXL - Vol II", Undated; ID: 157.0321; 158933 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0321)
    - "White Apache PXL", Undated; ID: 157.0322; 158932 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0322)
    - "Riefenstahl Recorded, Julie's, MTV Video Music Awards", Undated; ID: 157.0323; 158931 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0323)
    - "90210 - Just, Art School Chicks - None", Undated; ID: 157.0324; 158930 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0324)
    - "Sarah, Katie & Ali, Recorded TV Show First, (1987? 1989)", ID: 157.0326; 158929 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0326)
    - "Ally's Party Tape", Undated; ID: 157.0329; 158928 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0329)
    - "Apartment, Madison 1991, Sarah Raps", ID: 157.0330; 158927 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0330)
    - "Brighton Beach Memoirs, Edina High School, April 13-15, 1989", ID: 157.0331; 158926 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0331)
    - "Brit, Ally & Sarah Apr. 23, 1988", ID: 157.0332; 158925 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0332)
    - "(Blank) Sarah's Party, July '89 -Flashdancing, -Jen Reeves & Me, -Cory's Apt in NY (Boring)", 1989; ID: 157.0333; 158924 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0333)
    - "To: Sarah, From: Nardwvar, 'My life story...so far!'", Undated; ID: 157.0334; 158923 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0334)
    - "Fisher Price Tape, Filming SK 1992", ID: 157.0335; 158922 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0335)
    - "(Blank) Jenny Anderson, Joy Hagen, Sarah Jacobson, hour 6", Undated; ID: 157.0336; 158921 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0336)
    - "E-Day! Big Titles Chevy Chase", Undated; ID: 157.0337; 158920 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0337)
      TRT: 00:03:00
    - "Dogs in Space", Undated; ID: 157.0338; 158919 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0338)
    - "No Alternative Girls, Sonic Youth, Vida Loca, Luscious Jackson - Tamra", Undated; ID: 157.0348; 158918 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0348)
    - "South w/ Charles, McAllister Apt., Mount Tam", Undated; ID: 157.0351; 158917 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0351)
    - "White River Apache Vol. 1", Undated; ID: 157.0353; 158916 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0353)
    - "#3 Radical / Rally 1", Undated; ID: 157.0429; 158915 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0429)
    - "DV 4 Rally 2 [No Sound]", Undated; ID: 157.0430; 158914 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0430)
    - "State Fair Reunion 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0433; 158913 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0433)
    - "Mpls Grumpy's State Fair 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0434; 158912 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0434)
    - "Anton El Mack, Reunion After Party 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0436; 158911 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0436)
    - "Album Covers 2000", ID: 157.0455; 158910 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0455)
    - "Bra Shopping PXL Tape", Undated; ID: 157.0456; 158909 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0456)
    - "Candy Snatchers, Shot by SJ, Camera Mike 8/8/00", 2000; ID: 157.0458; 158908 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0458)
    - "My Apartment Willis Project 11/11/00", 2000; ID: 157.0461; 158907 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0461)
    - Lunachicks Videos, [1] "Say What You Mean" [2] "Naked", Undated; ID: 157.0462; 158906 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0462)
    - "Law + Order 10/2000, Gorilla Girls", ID: 157.0464; 158905 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0464)
    - "Le Tigre, Law + Order 10/00", 2000; ID: 157.0465; 158904 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0465)
    - "Riot Headline", Undated; ID: 157.0466; 158903 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0466)
    - "Rosewood Poetry Reading [No Sound]", Undated; ID: 157.0467; 158902 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0467)
    - "Ali's Apt Rap Flashdance", Undated; ID: 157.0468; 158901 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0468)
    - "Arin + Her Friends: In Her Room, Phone Chat, Boys, Mall, Town, Porto's Pizza, Delaware City 11/99", 1999; ID: 157.0469; 158900 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0469)
    - "In SF Before Moving: [1] Selling Books [2] Car Wash [3] Garage Sale [4] Christian Film Cafe [5] Jack Stevenson at LaRondella [6] Bank Deposit [7] Greg in Union Sq. [8] Haircut - Timecode Break [9] Learning Annex Class [10] AIDS Test [11] MAC - Buying Make-Up [12] SF Beach [13] Canyon Cinema [14] Sunny's Office [15] Gillman MJ Show", Undated; ID: 157.0470; 158899 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0470)
    - "SF, etc: [1] MAX [2] On the Bus [3] Swing Dancing [4] Punk Basketball [5] Willie Brown 10/99", 1999; ID: 157.0471; 158898 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0471)
    - "Me + Tony at CBGBs 4/27/2001", ID: 157.0472; 158897 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0472)
    - "Moving from Sublet to 347, Editing Fiasco, Mom in NY / Sublet, Manhattan Mini, New Movie, Cable Eric, Eric's a Dick, Feel Better, Bossitogg Drill, New Storage, Hitairi, Mama Said, New Studio, 12/2-17/99", 1999; ID: 157.0473; 158896 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0473)
    - "Lori's House, Kristin T., 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0474; 158895 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0474)
    - "Sunny + Kevin's Wedding, Liz Shoots Clone Other * People 9/99", 1999; ID: 157.0475; 158894 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0475)
    - "Private Projections by Brian Chang [Blank]", Undated; ID: 157.0476; 158893 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0476)
    - "Barefoot Cont. [Blank]", Undated; ID: 157.0477; 158892 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0477)
    - "C.B.D. 006 [Blank]", Undated; ID: 157.0478; 158891 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0478)
    - "BBW 005", Undated; ID: 157.0479; 158890 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0479)
    - "Hospice Interview 1/29/04", 2004; ID: 157.0500; 158889 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0500)
      Notation inside original housing indicates that Sarah did this interview two weeks before she died.
      Format: DVD, Donated Element
  - Subseries E: Computer Discs, 158867
    This subseries includes floppy discs. Notation on original housing indicates that Sarah wrote Popcorn and later Mary Jane drafts on this format, between 1990-1991 at Bard College.
    - Appleworks Preboot v2.0, 1990-1991; 158887 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0001)
      Format: Scotch Floppy Disk, Donated Element
    - Appleworks Program v2.0, 1990-1991; 158886 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0002)
    - Unidentified BASF Diskette, 1990-1991; 158885 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0003)
      Format: BASF Diskette, Donated Element
    - Unidentified Kodak Diskette, 1990-1991; 158884 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0004)
      Format: Kodak Diskette, Donated Element
    - "Interactive Systems, Inc.," Scotch Diskette, 1990-1991; 158883 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0005)
    - Data Disk II, 1990-1991; 158882 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0006)
      Format: Irish Floppy Disk, Donated Element
    - Data Disk No. 3, 1990-1991; 158881 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0007)
      Format: Irish Floppy Disk in Kodak Diskette Sleeve, Donated Element
    - "Free", 1990-1991; 158880 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0008)
      Format: Irish Floppy Disc in Scotch Diskette Sleeve, Donated Element
    - 2nd Copy, Chap. 1, 2, 3 Improved, 1990-1991; 158879 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0009)
      Format: BASF Floppy Disc in Kodak Diskette Sleeve, Donated Element
    - 2nd Copy Chap. 4, 5, 1990-1991; 158878 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0010)
      Format: BASF Floppy Disc, Donated Element
    - 2nd Copy, Chap. 6, 7, 1990-1991; 158877 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0011)
    - 2nd Copy, Chap. 8,9, 1990-1991; 158876 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0012)
    - 2nd Copy, Chap 10, 11, 1990-1991; 158875 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0013)
      Format: Floppy Disc, Donated Element
    - Early Writings 1980s, 158874 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0014)
      Format: TDK Disc, Donated Element
    - Early Writings Bard 1989-92, 1989-1992; 158873 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0015)
    - Writing 1995-1999, 158872 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0016)
    - From Computer 1, 2004; 158871 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0017)
    - Mary Jane, From Computer 2, 2004; 158870 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0018)
    - From Computer 3, 2004; 158869 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0019)
    - From Computer 4, 2004; 158868 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0020)
- Accretion 2008 - Series VII: Printed Material, 1990-2004; 158852
  - Assorted Published Clips, 1990-2002; 158865 (Box 21, Folder 159)
  - Homage and Obituary Press about Sarah G. Jacobson, 2004; 158864 (Box 21, Folder 160)
  - It's Your World - If You Don't Like It, Change It, Activism for Teenagers by Mikki Halpin, 2004; 158863 (Box 23, Folder 233)
    General Note
    Includes an inscription from the author.
  - Chris Gore's Ultimate Film Festival Survival Guide, 3rd Edition, 2004; 158862 (Box 23, Folder 234)
  - Girl Director by Andrea Richards, 2005; 158861 (Box 23, Folder 235)
    Includes a dedication to Jacobson.
  - Microfilm, The Magazine of Personal Cinema in Action #7, 2005; 158860 (Box 23, Folder 236)
  - SPIN Magazine, March 2002, 158859 (Box 23, Folder 237)
  - RAYGUN Magazine, #71 September 1999, 158858 (Box 23, Folder 238)
  - JANE Magazine, December 2001, 158857 (Box 23, Folder 239)